<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="eclipse_info_section_title">Where and When?</string>
    <string name="safety_warning">"Even a short glance at the sun can cause permanent eye damage. That’s also true during the first and last phases of an eclipse when the sun’s disk is partially covered. So while the dimmer light of a partial eclipse may tempt you, the only time you can safely view the sun is the short period called totality, when the sun is completely covered by the moon.     "</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement">I acknowledge that these photos and their locations will be part of a public database.</string>
    <string name="megamovie_directory_name">Eclipse_Camera_Images</string>
    <string name="upload_intro">Once you have captured images of the eclipse, you can upload them here to the Megamovie Archive.         This database will provide an invaluable tool for scientists studying our sun.</string>
    <string name="upload_notes">" Please note, it may take several seconds for the upload to start after pressing the button. Some files are large, so the upload may take a few minutes.     "</string>
    <string name="orientation_section_title">How to Use this App</string>
    <string name="about_section_title">About</string>
    <string name="gallery_section_title">Image Gallery</string>
    <string name="settings_section_title">Equipment Settings</string>
    <string name="moon_test_section_title">Practice Image Capture</string>
    <string name="calibration_section_title">Calibration</string>
    <string name="upload_section_title">Data Upload</string>
    <string name="capture_mode_section_title">Capture Mode</string>
    <string name="days">DAYS</string>
    <string name="hours">HOURS</string>
    <string name="minutes">MINUTES</string>
    <string name="seconds">SECONDS</string>
    <string name="right_on_time">Right on time</string>
    <string name="phases_prompt">Remember each contact during the eclipse.</string>
    <string name="first_contact">First Contact</string>
    <string name="first_contact_blurb">The beginning of the eclipse.</string>
    <string name="second_contact">Second Contact</string>
    <string name="second_contact_blurb">The beginning of totality.</string>
    <string name="mid_eclipse">Totality</string>
    <string name="mid_eclipse_blurb">The middle of the eclipse.</string>
    <string name="third_contact">Third contact</string>
    <string name="third_contact_blurb">The end of totality.</string>
    <string name="fourth_contact">Fourth contact:</string>
    <string name="fourth_contact_blurb">The end of the eclipse.</string>
    <string name="learn_more">LEARN MORE</string>
    <string name="credits_section_title">Credits</string>
    <string name="welcome_title">Eclipse Camera 2019</string>
    <string name="photo_credits">Photo Credits</string>
    <string name="photo_credits_text">Photos in the Phases section by Lorenzo Comolli and Alessandro Gambaro</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Citizen Science and the Megamovie Solar Image Archive</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="intro_text">On July 2, 2019, a total solar eclipse will be visible in South America. People in the narrow path of totality will see the sun\'s disk completely covered by the moon. This app makes it easy to be part of an exciting citizen-science project and capture great images of this amazing event.</string>
    <string name="intro_text_1">Everyone! This app does all the hard work of controlling your smartphone         camera to capture images of the eclipse at just the right times. You can use it with just your phone     or with an external lens and tripod to get even sharper images of this once-in-a-lifetime event.</string>
    <string name="intro_text_2">The app is very easy to use. You just have to point your phone in the right direction during the eclipse     and the app takes the pictures for you. If you have an external lens and tripod, the app will help you set everything up     to get the best shots possible.</string>
    <string name="intro_title_0">Welcome to Eclipse Camera 2019!</string>
    <string name="intro_title_1">Who is this app for?</string>
    <string name="intro_title_2">How do I use the app?</string>
    <string name="safety_warning_title">"Safety Warning     "</string>
    <string name="distance_to_totality_format">You are %d kilometers from the path of totality.</string>
    <string name="in_the_path_of_totality_string">You are in the path of totality!</string>
    <string name="search_bar_hint">Eclipse viewing location?</string>
    <string name="about_megamovie">"The Eclipse Camera 2019 app was created by Ideum, Inc. and UC Berkeley’s Space Sciences Laboratory.   This app allows you to capture images of the solar eclipse on July 2, 2019. The app can capture valuable scientific information without additional equipment. But you can obtain even better results with an external lens and tripod. If you already have this equipment or want to learn more, use our built-in Eclipse Orientation to customize the app.   If you are using an external lens and tripod, the app has a Calibration mode that will help you focus the lens and point the camera in the right direction. You can practice by capturing images of the moon. "</string>
    <string name="orientation_intro">"The Orientation mode helps you determine how best to use the app. Answer a few questions on the next screen to optimize your eclipse experience.     "</string>
    <string name="equipment_info_phone">"The Eclipse Camera app is designed to help you use your camera phone to take the best possible images of the solar eclipse. It tells you when and where to see the eclipse, how to aim your camera when the eclipse is about to start, and automatically controls your camera’s settings and shutter to take a series of photos during the event. All you’ll have to do is be ready and follow a few simple instructions when the time comes. The app also gives you a way to practice before the eclipse by taking pictures of the moon or sun, so you'll feel comfortable when the big day arrives. "</string>
    <string name="equipment_info_equipment">"Holding a camera by hand can cause tiny vibrations that blur photos. This can be especially troublesome with astronomical images. Mounting your phone on a tripod is an easy way to improve your photos. There are many kinds of tripods available for cell phones.\\n  Also, while your phone may have a great camera, images of the sun are likely to be small unless you use an external lens. We recommend using a lens with a magnification of at least 20x, although the app is compatible with any lens. Lenses like these are very portable and can help you take great photos of many things in addition to the eclipse. If you’re using an especially high-powered lens, you might consider using a tracking mount.\\n Once you’ve decided on the equipment you’ll use, go to My Eclipse settings to enter your choice (you can change it at any time).  "</string>
    <string name="equipment_info_dslr">If you want to use a separate camera to photograph the eclipse, you can still use the eclipse map and countdown functions in the Eclipse Camera 2019 app.</string>
    <string name="first_contact_dialog_message">"This is when the edge of the moon first begins to cover the sun. Even though the sun will start to get dimmer at this point it’s still not safe to look directly at the eclipse. "</string>
    <string name="second_contact_dialog_message">"In a total solar eclipse, this is when totality begins and the sun’s disk is completely covered by the moon. It is safe to remove your eclipse glasses when you can no longer see the bright sun through them. You can now see the sun’s hot, hazy outer atmosphere: the corona!  "</string>
    <string name="mid_eclipse_dialog_message">"The sun’s corona, a halo of ionized gases, extends millions of miles into space. At over 1 million degrees Fahrenheit, it is much hotter than the sun’s surface. You can only see the whole corona during a total eclipse, such as this one.    "</string>
    <string name="third_contact_dialog_message">Third contact is the moment when totality ends and the sun begins to emerge from the moon’s shadow. As soon as the bright sun appears, you must put your eclipse glasses back on.</string>
    <string name="fourth_contact_dialog_message">"This is the end of the eclipse. "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_intro">"By using the app to capture images of the moon or sun, you'll become familiar with how the app works and be ready to use it to photograph the main event: the solar eclipse. This will be especially helpful if you will be using an external lens and tripod during the eclipse. "</string>
    <string name="remove_case">Do you use a phone case? Calibration accuracy may be improved if you remove it.</string>
    <string name="practice_mode_ftp_request">To help the developers of this app, you can upload practice images         to ftp://apollo.ssl.berkeley.edu/pub/megamovie/incoming</string>
    <string name="practice_mode_target_selection_prompt">"Would you like to practice by taking pictures of the moon or sun? The conditions for these tests are quite different, so we recommend          practicing with both.     "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_select_time">"When would you like to start taking pictures of the moon or sun? We recommend choosing a time at least 20 minutes in the future. Note that the app will start taking pictures         3 minutes before your chosen time, and continue for 3 minutes afterwards.     "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_calibration">"If you don't have any extra equipment like a tripod or external lens, you can now enter Capture Mode.           If you have an external lens, the app can help you focus it correctly. If you are attaching your phone to         a tripod, the app can help you point the phone in the right direction.     "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_calibrate_lens_explanation">"If you are using an external lens, the app can help you focus it correctly.     "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_calibrate_direction_explanation">"If you aren't attaching your phone to a tripod, you can now enter Capture Mode.If you are attaching your phone to a tripod, the app can help you point the phone towards the location where the sun/moon will be at the time you selected.     "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_calibrate_direction">"Turn your phone in the direction of the red line. As you get closer to the correct direction,         the blue circle will get larger. The circle will turn green when your phone and tripod         are correctly calibrated. Then press Capture Mode.     "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_calibrate_lens">"Point the camera at an object that is more than 100 feet away, like a tree or a building.         Adjust the focus of the external lens until the object in the preview         appears crisp and in focus. You may adjust the brightness of the preview using the buttons         above.     "</string>
    <string name="moon_test_calibrate_compass_instructions">"Align the phone so the target appears in the center of the red crosshairs. Then press SET.     "</string>
    <string name="compass_calibration_intro">"The app will use your phone's compass to help point your camera in the right direction. To help calibrate the compass, move your phone in a series of quick figure-eight movements until the compass accuracy is high.     "</string>
    <string name="sun_test_warning">"Remember not to look directly at the sun during the test. Photographing the sun requires a solar filter or eclipse glasses to cover the lens. If it is         a hot day, be careful not to leave your phone outside for too long.     "</string>
    <string name="eclipse_day_intro_fragment_title">Eclipse Image Capture</string>
    <string name="eclipse_day_intro">The app can help you capture photos of the eclipse, and share them to the Megamovie Archive for scientific study.           The app will capture about 1GB worth of images, so make sure you have enough storage available on your phone.  Once you have entered Capture Mode,     the app will give an audio alert 15 seconds before the start of totality reminding you to remove your solar filter.</string>
    <string name="check_for_updates">Please check you have the most recent version of the app the day before the eclipse!</string>
    <string name="eclipse_day_instructions">"The app will take pictures only during totality, when the sun is completely covered by the moon. During totality, you just not cover the lens with a solar filter. However, before totality you will need a filter to protect your phone. The app will remind you with an audio         cue to remove the filter 15 seconds before the start of totality.     "</string>
    <string name="equipment_intro">The app can help you set up your equipment. If you don\'t need help with this, you can go         directly to Capture Mode.           Remember to use a solar filter when pointing your lens. The app will remind you to remove it 15 seconds before the start of totality.</string>
    <string name="eclipse_day_skip_set_up">If you have already set up your equipment or would like to skip this step, you can go     directly to capture mode</string>
    <string name="eclipse_day_no_equipment">"It looks you aren't using any extra equipment, so do not have to do any additional set-up.     "</string>
    <string name="eclipse_day_calibrate_direction_explanation">"If you are using a tripod, the app can help you point your phone towards the point in the sky where the eclipse will occur.     "</string>
    <string name="eclipse_day_calibrate_compass_instructions">"Align the phone so the sun appears in the center of the red crosshairs. Then press SET.     "</string>
    <string name="user_mode_default">Phone only</string>
    <string name="lens_default">No external lens</string>
    <string name="optimize_your_eclipse_photography">Optimize your eclipse photography</string>
    <string name="lens_magnification_pref_key">lens magnification</string>
    <string name="tripod_default">No tripod</string>
    <string name="no_tripod_warning">"If you plan to attach an external lens to your smartphone, you will also need to mount it on a tripod to ensure it is kept steady and pointed in the right direction.     "</string>
    <string name="camera_not_supported_warning">Unfortunately, your phone\'s camera does not support manual control of its sensors,     so the app will be unable to capture images of the eclipse. You can still use the other features of the app, however, including     the eclipse map and eclipse timing information.</string>
    <string name="ideum_credit">"Ideum is a creative company focused on using emerging technologies to design public installations and products that lead to meaningful and  compelling user experiences. We work with museums, Fortune 500 companies, and other entities throughout North America and around the world. Our firm provides design services, custom software development, interactive displays, touch tables, and audio-visual (A/V) solutions. "</string>
    <string name="ssl_credit">The Space Sciences Laboratory (SSL) is the UC system’s premier space sciences research facility and one of the preeminent university laboratories in the country for space research. Its primary goal is to foster outstanding research in space-related  sciences and to provide education for the next generation of space scientists.         Research at SSL is led by Berkeley faculty and SSL Senior Fellows, and focuses on  experiments and observations carried out in space, but also includes research with the potential of leading to future space experiments, and the theoretical research that is tied into their experimental and observational programs.</string>
    <string name="eaa_credit" translatable="true">" Eclipse Across America, Inc. is a non-profit founded by filmmaker/director and eclipse chaser Mark Bender. "</string>
    <string name="moon">moon</string>
    <string name="sun">sun</string>
    <string name="got_it">GOT IT</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="countdown">COUNTDOWN</string>
    <string name="phases">PHASES</string>
    <string name="not_in_path_toast">This location is not within the path of totality</string>
    <string name="not_in_path_toast_1">This location is in the path of totality! Go to Phases to see the eclipse timing. This location is %.0f km away.</string>
    <string name="distance_from_path_toast">You are %.0f km from the path of totality.  Go to Phases to see the eclipse timing.</string>
    <string name="calibrate_your_compass">Calibrate your compass</string>
    <string name="compass_accuracy">Compass Accuracy</string>
    <string name="high">high</string>
    <string name="low">low</string>
    <string name="medium">medium</string>
    <string name="unreliable">unreliable</string>
    <string name="cant_tell_accuracy">can\'t tell accuracy</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>
    <string name="test_time_not_set_alert">Please set a time and date for the test</string>
    <string name="test_time_in_future_alert">Please schedule your test at least 5 minutes in the future.</string>
    <string name="calibrate_lens">Calibrate Lens</string>
    <string name="calibrate_direction">Calibrate Direction</string>
    <string name="capture_mode">Capture Mode</string>
    <string name="dimmer">dimmer</string>
    <string name="done">done</string>
    <string name="brighter">brighter</string>
    <string name="set">set</string>
    <string name="solar_filter_warning">Make sure your lens is covered with a solar filter.</string>
    <string name="images_captured">Images captured</string>
    <string name="test_congrats_message">Congratulations! You captured %d images. You can find them in a new album in your photo app.</string>
    <string name="test_time_start">Test time start</string>
    <string name="test_time_alert">Your test is scheduled to occur in</string>
    <string name="finish">finish</string>
    <string name="photographing_the_eclipse">Photographing the Eclipse</string>
    <string name="how_will_you_photograph_the_eclipse">How will you capture the eclipse?</string>
    <string name="only_my_phone">only my phone</string>
    <string name="my_phone_with_peripheral_equipment">My phone with peripheral equipment</string>
    <string name="a_dslr_camera">A DSLR camera</string>
    <string name="what_equipment_will_you_use">What equipment will you use to photograph the eclipse?</string>
    <string name="not_in_path_warning">You are not currently in the path of totality!</string>
    <string name="in_path_alert">You are in the path of totality!</string>
    <string name="Equipment">Equipment</string>
    <string name="how_do_you_plan">How will you capture the eclipse?</string>
    <string name="external_lens_magnification">External lens magnification</string>
    <string name="tracking_mount">Tracking Mount</string>
    <string name="tripod">Tripod</string>
    <string name="yes">yes</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="phone_only">phone only</string>
    <string name="phone_with_equipment">phone with equipment</string>
    <string name="dslr">dslr</string>
    <string name="ok">ok</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="equipment_setup">Equipment Setup</string>
    <string name="start_of_totality">"Start of totality: "</string>
    <string name="go_to_upload_screen">Go to upload screen</string>
    <string name="not_in_path_dialog">Eclipse image capture is only available within the path of totality</string>
    <string name="eclipse_congrats_message">Congratulations! You captured %d images. You can find them in a new album in your photo app.</string>
    <string name="image_upload">Image Upload</string>
    <string name="no_image_upload_warning">You do not currently have any images to upload. Please return after photographing the eclipse.</string>
    <string name="license">I verify that I own these photos and am licensing them under the</string>
    <string name="you_have_d_photos_to_upload">You currently have %d files ready to upload to the archive.</string>
    <string name="files_uploaded">Files Uploaded: %d/%d</string>
    <string name="upload_errors">Upload errors: %d</string>
    <string name="no_network_connection_found">No network connection found</string>
    <string name="upload_complete">Upload Complete</string>
    <string name="upload">upload</string>
    <string name="using_your_smartphone">Using your smartphone</string>
    <string name="eclipse_photo_gear">Eclipse photo gear</string>
    <string name="dslr_eclipse_photography">DSLR eclipse photography</string>
    <string name="capturing_the_eclipse_with_your_phone">Capturing the eclipse with your phone</string>
    <string name="equipment_for_eclipse_photography">Equipment for eclipse photography</string>
    <string name="capture_stunning_eclipse_photos">Capture stunning eclipse photos</string>
    <string name="equipment_info_gear">Holding a camera by hand can cause tiny vibrations that blur photos. This can be especially troublesome with astronomical images. Mounting your phone on a tripod is an easy way to improve your photos. There are many kinds of tripods available for cell phones. \n\n Also, while your phone may have a great camera, images of the sun are likely to be small unless you use an external lens. We recommend using a lens with a magnification of at least 20x, although the app is compatible with any lens. Lenses like these are very portable and can help you take great photos of many things in addition to the eclipse. If you’re using an especially high-powered lens, you might consider using a tracking mount.\n\n Once you’ve decided on the equipment you’ll use, go to My Eclipse settings to enter your choice (you can change it at any time).</string>
    <string name="equipment_settings">equipment settings</string>
    <string name="countdown_explanation">This feature shows you the time remaining before totality begins at your selected location, as marked by the red pin.</string>
    <string name="enable_location_services">Please note: location services must be enabled on your phone in order to automatically calculate eclipse timing. Otherwise, you can choose a location manually by tapping a location in the path of totality.</string>
    <string name="only_phone_explanation">This is the easiest way to use the app, but will likely have the worst picture quality</string>
    <string name="my_phone_with_peripheral_equipment_explanation">A lens and a tripod will allow for higher quality photos, but takes extra setup and calibration.</string>
    <string name="a_dslr_camera_explanation">If you are using a DSLR camera, the map and countdown features of this application can still be used.</string>
</resources>